Guide to the The Nick Zedd Papers 1963 - 2010 MSS.311
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VIII: Film, 214740
  - Subseries A: By Nick Zedd, 214757
    - "Police State" [Unmarked White Reel], 1987; ID: 311.0054; 215692 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0054)
    - "Police State" [Unmarked Reel], 1987; ID: 311.0053; 215691 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0053)
    - "Police State - Color Reversal B-Wind Head", c1987; ID: 311.0448; 215645 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0448)
    - "Whoregasm Original", c1988; ID: 311.0042; 215641 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0042)
    - "Whoregasm - Right Original", c1988; ID: 311.0056; 215642 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0056)
    - "Nick Zedd - No Title", June 13, 1988; ID: 311.0043; 215640 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0043)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Outtakes: Soldier Baby", 1992; ID: 311.0044; 215678 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0044)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Workprint for Camera Rolls #3 and #1", 1992; ID: 311.0045; 215676 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0045)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Outtakes: Kembra, Richard Chudnon, Annie Sprinkle", 1992; ID: 311.0046; 215677 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0046)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Work Print Postive Roll A2", April 30, 1993; ID: 311.0047; 215684 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0047)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Work Print Postive Octopus Cult, Dwarf, Ari Face, Roll A1", April 30, 1993; ID: 311.0048; 215685 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0048)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Work Print Positive Roll A4", April 30, 1993; ID: 311.0049; 215686 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0049)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Work Print Positive Roll A3", April 30, 1993; ID: 311.0050; 215687 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0050)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy" [unmarked], October 18, 1990; ID: 311.0057; 215632 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0057)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy" [unmarked], October 18, 1990; ID: 311.0058; 215631 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0058)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Dwarf", October 18, 1990; ID: 311.0059; 215628 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0059)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Octopus Cult Workprint Negative IMP", October 18, 1990; ID: 311.0060; 215629 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0060)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy" [unmarked], October 18, 1990; ID: 311.0061; 215630 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0061)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Tails Out Octopus Cult and Dwarf Negative", April 30, 1993; ID: 311.0062; 215633 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0062)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - A1 Contact Print Capt. Zero", January 11, 1993; ID: 311.0063; 215634 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0063)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Workprint", April 22, 1993; ID: 311.0064; 215635 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0064)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Credits, Kembra Fish, TV Footage, Credits Negative", July 2, 1992; ID: 311.0065; 215636 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0065)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Credits, Kembra and Fish, Credits Negative", July 3, 1992; ID: 311.0066; 215637 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0066)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy 3 - Workprint", c1992; ID: 311.0067; 215638 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0067)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy 4 - World's Fair Negative", c1992; ID: 311.0068; 215639 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0068)
    - "Lock Stock and Barrel" by Nick Zedd, Emma Diamond, and Mark Brady, 1994; ID: 311.0069; 215683 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0069)
    - "Squeezebox '95 - R2 Negative", 1995; ID: 311.0070; 215682 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0070)
      Squeezebox '95 - R2 Negative
    - "Squeezebox 1 & 2", 1995; ID: 311.0071; 215681 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0071)
    - "Screen Tests - A Roll", January 1998; ID: 311.0072; 215649 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0072)
    - "Screen Tests - Salonge, Daryl, Karen, Bob B Roll", January 1998; ID: 311.0073; 215648 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0073)
    - "Why Do You Exist" [Unmarked Reel], 1998; ID: 311.0074; 215702 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0074)
    - "Why Do You Exist" [Unmarked Reel], 1998; ID: 311.0075; 215703 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0075)
    - "Why Do You Exist" [Unmarked Reel], 1998; ID: 311.0077; 215705 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0077)
    - "Ecstasy in Entropy - Heads Original", c1999; ID: 311.0078; 215646 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0078)
    - "Ecstasy in Entropy - Head Original", c1999; ID: 311.0079; 215647 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0079)
    - "Ecstasy in Entropy - Outtakes", 2001; ID: 311.0083; 215707 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0083)
    - "Imitation of Kiss [I of K9]", 2001; ID: 311.0001; 215563 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0001)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf: Behind the Scenes Bluescreen Footage Negative", undated; ID: 311.0080; 215643 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0080)
    - "Japan", undated; ID: 311.0081; 215679 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0081)
    - "Mixed Misc. Footage", undated; ID: 311.0082; 215680 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0082)
    - "Roll A Film Test Nick Zedd", undated; ID: 311.0090; 215711 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0090)
    - "Rose PG-36", undated; ID: 311.0085; 215708 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0085)
    - [Unidentified Color Film], undated; ID: 311.0086; 215709 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0086)
    - [Collection of Three Unidentified Film Reels], undated; ID: 311.0087 - 311.0089; 215710 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0087 - 311.0089)
    - [Unidentified B&W Film Reel], undated; ID: 311.0091; 215712 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0091)
  - Subseries B: Original Containers, 215469
    - "Pierre Ganzel's Imitation of Kiss" by Nick Zedd [Black TDK Container], 2001; 215566 (Box 19A)
      Original Housing for Media ID: 311.0001
    - "The Bogus Man" [Rockingham County Public Library Metal Container with Gray Plastic Film Reel Holder], 1980; 215567 (Box 19A)
      Original Housing for Media ID: 311.0002a - 311.0002b.
    - "Original Nomad" [Eastman Kodak Company Metal Container with Black Plastic Film Reel Holder], undated; 215568 (Box 19A)
      Media ID: 311.0005, originally found empty with "Nomad" Media ID: 311.0004.
    - "Destination X" [Eastman Kodak Canister], 1976; 216755 (Box 19A)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0003.
    - "Nomad" [Metal Film Canister], 1978; 216756 (Box 19A)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0004.
    - "They Eat Scum" [Anthology Film Archives Canister], 1979; 216762 (Box 19B)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0006.
    - "They Eat Scum" [Eastman/Anthology Film Archives Canister], 1979; 216763 (Box 19B)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0007a - 311.0007b.
    - "They Eat Scum - Outtakes" [Plastic Canister], 1979; 216757 (Box 19A)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0008.
    - "They Eat Scum" [Eastman Kodak Canister], 1979; 216758 (Box 19A)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0009 - 311.0011.
    - "They Eat Scum" [35mm Kodak Canister], 1979; 216760 (Box 19B)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0012 - 311.0013.
    - "They Eat Scum" [35mm Kodak Canister], 1979; 216761 (Box 19B)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0014 - 311.0015.
    - "The Wild World of Lydia Lunch" [Super 8 Canister], 1983; 216759 (Box 19A)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0016.
    - "Police State - Fill" [Scotch Magnetic Film Box], 1987; 217826 (Box 19B)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0026, 311.0028.
    - "Police State - Scene Two Coded Dailies" [White Box], 1987; 217827 (Box 19A)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0032.
    - "Police Sate Cut Work Pix" [White Box], 1987; 217828 (Box 19A)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0034 - 311.0035.
    - "Police State - Fill" [White Box], 1987; 217829 (Box 19A)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0037 - 311.0039.
    - "Police State Dial A & B" [White Box], 1987; 217830 (Box 19B)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0040 - 311.0041.
    - "Police State" [Anthology Film Archives Metal Canister], 2011; 218956 (Box 19C)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0447 - 311.0448.
    - "No Title - June 14th 1988" [Du Art Film Box], 217831 (Box 19B)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0043.
    - "Whoregasm - Original" [Kin-O-Lux Inc. Box], 1988; 217929 (Box 19A)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0042, 311.0056.
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Workprint for Camera Rolls 3 and 1", 1990s; 224516 (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0045.
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Outtakes Kembra" [Metal Precision Film Cannister and Reel], 1990s; 221140 (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0046.
    - "War Is Menstrual Envy Workprint Positive" [Cardboard Box], 1993; 221137 (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0047 - 311.0050.
    - "War - Tails Out" [Du Art Film Box], 1993; 217930 (Box 19B)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0062.
    - "War is Menstrual Envy" [Du Art Film Box], 1993; 217931 (Box 19B)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0063.
    - "War" [Precision Film Laboratories Box], 1990; 218178 (Box 19C)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0057 - 311.0061.
    - "War is Menstrual Envy" [Du Art Film Box], 1993; 218217 (Box 19C)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0064.
    - "War: Credits + Kembra" [Du Art Film Box], 1990 - 1992; 218218 (Box 19C)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0065.
    - "War: Credits, Kembra + Fish" [Du Art Film Box], 1992; 218219 (Box 19C)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0066.
    - "War is Menstrual Envy" [Du Art Film Box], 1993; 218220 (Box 19C)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0067.
    - "War: World's Fair", 1993; 218221 (Box 19C)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0068.
    - "Lock, Stock and Barrel" [Blue Film Cannister with Metal Reel], 1995; 221136 (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0069.
    - "Squeezebox '95 - R2 Negative", 1995; 224515 (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID 311.0070.
    - "1995 Squeezebox" [Du Art Film Box], 221138 (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0071.
    - "Why Do You Exist" [Kodak Metal Canister], 1998; 218177 (Box 19C)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0074 - 311.0075, 311.0077.
    - "Screen Tests" [Du Art Film Box], 1998; 218222 (Box 19C)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0072.
    - "Screen Tests - B Roll" [Du Art Film Box], 1998; 218223 (Box 19C)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0073.
    - "Ecstasy in Entropy" [Kodak Metal Canister], 1999; 218955 (Box 19A)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0078 - 311.0079.
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf" [Fuji Metal Canister], 2003; 218954 (Box 19A)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0080.
    - "Japan" [Gold Metal Cannister and Reel], undated; 221139 (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0081.
    - "Mixed Misc. Footage" [Brown metal Film Cannister], undated; 221135 (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0082.
    - "Psycolor" [Paper Box], 1970; 224521 (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0092.
    - "Harding Productions Inc: Attack of The Giant Fly and Cartoon" [Paper Box], 1968; 224517 (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0105.
    - "The Giant Fly Invincible - Part 1" [Metal Canister], 1971; 224518 (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0106.
    - "The Giant Fly Invincible - Part 2" [Metal Canister], 1971; 224519 (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0107.
    - "The Giant Fly Invincible" [Illustrated Metal Canister], 1971; 224520 (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0108.
    - "Film Epics Volume 1: Harding Productions Inc, Flash Gordon" [Paper Box], 1970; 224522 (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0112.
    - "Worm Movie" by Lung Leg [Kodak Paper Box], undated; 224523 (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0132.
  - Subseries C: Juvenilia and Family, 214759
    - "Harding Productions Inc: Attack of The Giant Fly and Cartoon", 1968; ID: 311.0105; 215698 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0105)
      Format: 8mm
    - "Film Epics Volume 1: Harding Productions Inc, Flash Gordon", 1970; ID: 311.0112; 215699 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0112)
    - "Psycolor", 1970; ID: 311.0092; 215694 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0092)
    - "Psycolor" [Painted Reel], 1970; ID: 311.0084; 215706 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0084)
      Format: Handpainted 16mm Clear Reel
    - "The Giant Fly Invincible - Part 1", 1971; ID: 311.0106; 215695 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0106)
    - "The Giant Fly Invincible - Part 2", 1971; ID: 311.0107; 215696 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0107)
    - "The Giant Fly Invincible" [Illustrated Canister], 1971; ID: 311.0108; 215697 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0108)
    - "Grimy Underpants: An Atrocity by James Harding", undated; ID: 311.0117; 224238 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0117)
    - [Harding Family Films], 1956 - 1972; 215700 (Box 20)
      This is a collection of 21 Harding Family recordings.
      Media ID: 311.0093 - 311.0104, 311.0109 - 311.0111, 311.0113 - 311.0116, 311.000118 - 311.0119.
  - Subseries D: Miscellaneous, 214761
    - "Worm Movie" by Lung Leg, undated; ID: 311.0132; 215693 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0132)
    - [Commercial Films], undated; 215701 (Box 20)
      18 commercial films from Zedd's personal collection.
      Media ID: 311.0115 - 311.0116, 311.0118 - 311.0131, 311.0133 - 311.0134
  - Subseries E: Film Documentation, 216765
    - Laboratory Forms, 216766 (Box 19D)
- Series IX: Video recordings, 214741
  Series IX: Video includes original moving image elements by Zedd and is organized chronologically, then alphabetically.
  Subseries B: Acting and Press preserves Zedd's acting work, in addition to interviews and documentaries about the Cinema of Transgression by other filmmakers.
  Subseries C: Miscellaneous includes assorted footage from Zedd's personal video library, rare work by his contemporaries and collaborators, as well as commercial works that Zedd collected.
  - Subseries A: By Nick Zedd, 214762
    - "Giant Fly Films", 1968 - 1971; ID: 311.0376; 215907 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0376)
      Format: DVD-R
    - "Destination X - A Roll", 1977; ID: 311.0135; 215732 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0135)
      Format: VHS
    - "Destination X - A Roll", 1976 - 1977; ID: 311.0454; 215921 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0454)
    - "They Eat Scum - Part 1", 1979; ID: 311.0136; 215713 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0136)
      Format: U-Matic
      TRT: [01:15:00]
    - "They Eat Scum - Part II", 1979; ID: 311.0137; 215726 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0137)
      Format: Sony U-Matic
    - "They Eat Scum - Pt 1 & Pt 2, Bogus Man, Thrust in Me", April 2009; ID: 311.0138; 215714 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0138)
      Format: Digital Betacam
      TRT: [01:33:00]
    - "They Eat Scum", 1979; ID: 311.0377; 215915 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0377)
    - "The Bogus Man", 1980; ID: 311.0139; 215715 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0139)
      Format: MRX UCA-20
    - "The Bogus Man," "Thrust in Me" [Submaster One], 1980; ID: 311.0140; 215716 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0140)
      Format: Ampex U-Matic
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo - Reel One", 1983; ID: 311.0141; 215717 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0141)
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo - Part 2", 1983; ID: 311.0142; 215718 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0142)
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo - B&W PAL Master", undated; ID: 311.0143; 215731 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0143)
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo - Reel Two Colorlab Transfer", 2002; ID: 311.0144; 215730 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0144)
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo (Master)", 1983; ID: 311.0145; 215729 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0145)
      TRT: [01:10:00]
    - "Geek Maggo Bingo - Photo Gallery", undated; ID: 311.0146; 215728 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0146)
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo - Paul Tzenkle Interview with Brenda Bergman, Richard Hell, Donna Death, Nick Zedd", 1983; ID: 311.0147; 215727 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0147)
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo", 1983; ID: 311.0378; 215914 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0378)
    - "The Wild World of Lydia Lunch", 1983; ID: 311.0148; 215719 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0148)
      Format: Fuji Videocassette
      TRT: [00:28:00]
    - "The Wild World of Lydia Lunch," "Police State," "Whoregasm" [Submaster Tape Two], 1983 - 1988; ID: 311.0149; 215720 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0149)
    - "The Wild World of Lydia Lunch (Improved Version)," "Bogus Man," " School of Shame (Excerpt)", 1980 - 1984; ID: 311.0150; 215721 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0150)
      Format: Betacam SP
    - "The Wild World of Lydia Lunch and Other Films by Nick Zedd", 1980 - 1984; ID: 311.0151; 215722 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0151)
      TRT: [00:60:00]
    - "The Wild World of Lydia Lunch (Needs Sound)", 1983; ID: 311.0152; 215733 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0152)
    - "The Wild World of Lydia Lunch, " "Bogus Man" [Unopened Penetration Films Screeners Version], 1980 - 1983; ID: 311.0153; 215734 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0153)
      TRT: [00:39:00]
    - "The Wild World of Lydia Lunch - Interview Master", 1980 - 1989; ID: 311.0154; 215735 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0154)
    - "The Wild World of Lydia Lunch - Master Tape", 1980 - 1984; ID: 311.0155; 215736 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0155)
    - "Master - Wild World of Lydia Lunch, Etc.", 1980 - 1989; ID: 311.0156; 215737 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0156)
      Contents: "Bogus Man," "The Wild World of Lydia Lunch," "Kiss Me Goodbye," "Go to Hell," "Thrust in Me," "Radio Thin Air Interview with Nick Zedd, Claudia T.V."
    - "King of Sex," "Thrust in Me," "Kiss Me Goodbye," "Go to Hell", 1984 - 1986; ID: 311.0157; 215725 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0157)
    - "King of Sex," "Thrust in Me," "Kiss Me Goodbye," "Go To Hell", 1984 - 1986; ID: 311.0158; 215723 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0158)
    - "King of Sex," "Thrust in Me," "Kiss Me Goodbye," "Go to Hell" (Master Tape), 1984 - 1986; ID: 311.0159; 215738 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0159)
    - "Me Minus You", July 12, 1985; ID: 311.0160; 215724 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0160)
      Format: Beta Videocassette
    - "Me Minus You Plus 'Dear Cunt' with Zedd, Legere, Pryor", July 12, 1985; ID: 311.0161; 215739 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0161)
    - "Wanna Go Out? Richard Hell + Nick Zedd, Blank Generation, Ultra's, Brando in Court", c1987; ID: 311.0374; 215969 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0374)
    - "Police State - Master Tape", June 1, 1994; ID: 311.0162; 215800 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0162)
      TRT: [00:18:00]
    - "Twenty Something Program 2 - Reel 2", January 15, 1988; ID: 311.0163; 215799 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0163)
      Format: Sony BRS
      Contents: "Police State" and "Whoregasm" by Nick Zedd, "The Cowboy Stories" and "Cornella, Story of a Burning Bush" by Kembra Phaler
    - "Police State - PAL Master", 1987; ID: 311.0164; 215814 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0164)
    - "Police State (Old Scratched Master)", 1987; ID: 311.0165; 215820 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0165)
    - "Rubric Records 'Police State' ", October 16, 2000; ID: 311.0166; 215815 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0166)
      TRT: [00:20:50]
    - "Whoregasm", 1988; ID: 311.0379; 215916 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0379)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Part 1", May 12, 1992; ID: 311.0167; 215798 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0167)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Part 2", May 12, 1992; ID: 311.0168; 215797 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0168)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy (CV Master)", 1992; ID: 311.0169; 215796 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0169)
      TRT: [01:18:00]
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Part One (Master)", 1992; ID: 311.0170; 215795 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0170)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Part Two (Edited Final Master with End Credits and Ronnettes Music", 1992; ID: 311.0171; 215794 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0171)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Part II (Master)", 1992; ID: 311.0172; 215793 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0172)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Part III (Underwater Footage Original)", 1992; ID: 311.0173; 215792 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0173)
      Format: Ampex U-Matic SP
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Part III (Credits, Underwater Footage, 3/4 in. Unedited No Music - Master)", c1992; ID: 311.0174; 215791 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0174)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Part III (Opening Credits and Kembra Underwater with Metal Machine Music and End Credits", April 1992; ID: 311.0175; 215813 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0175)
      Format: Ampex U-matic
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Part I (Incomplete, Kembra is Missing, Water Footage Gone)", 1992; ID: 311.0176; 215812 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0176)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Parts I, II, and III PAL Master", 1990 - 1992; ID: 311.0177; 215819 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0177)
      TRT: [01:17:00]
    - "War is Menstrual Envy (Rank Syntel Master)", May 12, 1992; ID: 311.0225; 215895 (Box 24, Media ID: 311.0225)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy", 1992; ID: 311.0380; 215913 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0380)
    - "Screen Tests", January 1998; ID: 311.0187; 215858 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0187)
      Format: Sony U-Matic SP
    - "Screen Tests, A.K.A. Why Do You Exist - (Master)", January 1998; ID: 311.0188; 215850 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0188)
    - "Why Do You Exist (Master)", 1998; ID: 311.0189; 215859 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0189)
    - "Screen Tests (Silent)", c1998; ID: 311.0190; 215860 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0190)
    - "Tom Thumb in the Land of the Giants", 1999; ID: 311.0178; 215821 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0178)
      TRT: [00:04:30]
    - "Tom Thumb in the Land of the Giants (Master)", c1999; ID: 311.0179; 215822 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0179)
    - "Tom Thumb in the Land of the Giants (PAL Master Without Credits)", 1999; ID: 311.0180; 215823 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0180)
    - "Tom Thumb in the Land of the Giants - PAL Original", May 26, 1999; ID: 311.0181; 215818 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0181)
    - "Credits: Tom Thumb, Ecstasy in Entropy", undated; ID: 311.0182; 215817 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0182)
    - "Ecstasy in Entropy and Tom Thumb Credits", undated; ID: 311.0183; 215801 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0183)
      Format: Maxwell KCA - 10BQ
    - "Ecstasy in Entropy - Unedited HBO Footage of Nick Zedd Shooting with Annie Sprinkle, Brenda Bergman, Will Keenan", November 2, 1998; ID: 311.0184; 215816 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0184)
    - "Ecstasy in Entropy - Master Tape", 1999; ID: 311.0185; 215741 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0185)
    - "Abnormal: The Sinema of Nick Zedd", c1987; ID: 311.0198; 215874 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0198)
    - "Abnormal: The Sinema of Nick Zedd", 2001; ID: 311.0382; 215911 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0382)
      Format: DVD
    - "Generation Z: The Movies of Nick Zedd (CV Master)", c1999; ID: 311.0199; 215855 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0199)
      TRT: [01:27:00]
    - "Generation Z (PAL)", undated; ID: 311.0200; 215873 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0200)
    - "Generation Z: The Movies of Nick Zedd", c1999; ID: 311.0201; 215856 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0201)
    - "Rubric Records 'Imitation of Kiss' ", January 29, 2001; ID: 311.0186; 215740 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0186)
      TRT: [00:02:45]
    - "Lord of the Cockrings (Submaster Dub)", 2001; ID: 311.0191; 215851 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0191)
    - "Lord of the Cockrings", 2001; ID: 311.0381; 215912 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0381)
    - "Thus Spake Zarathustra (Master)", 2001; ID: 311.0192; 215868 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0192)
      Format: Hi8 MP Videocassette
    - "Thus Spake Zarathustra (Master)" by Nick Zedd and Jon Vomit, 2001; ID: 311.0193; 215861 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0193)
    - "Thus Spake Zarathustra", c2001; ID: 311.0194; 215870 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0194)
    - "Thus Spake Zarathustra", undated; ID: 311.0226; 215896 (Box 24, Media ID: 311.0226)
      TRT: [00:45:03]
    - "Elf Panties: The Movie (Master)", 2001; ID: 311.0231; 215899 (Box 24, Media ID: 311.0231)
      TRT: [00:08:06]
    - "Elf Panties and Lord of the Cockrings", c2001; ID: 311.0230; 215900 (Box 24, Media ID: 311.0230)
    - "I Was a Quality of Life Violation (Master)", November 18, 2002; ID: 311.0195; 215857 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0195)
    - "I Was a Quality of Life Violation", 2002; ID: 311.0196; 215871 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0196)
    - "I Was a Quality of Life Violation (Master)", 2002; ID: 311.0197; 215872 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0197)
      TRT: [00:35:00]